{
    "subject": "resource/Silicon_Graphics",
    "predicate": "property/url",
    "object": "//www.sgi.com",
    "human_readable": "The URL of Silicon Graphics is //www.sgi.com.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8457852602005005,
            "question": "Provide the URL of Silicon Graphics' official website."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.816820502281189,
            "question": "What is the URL of Silicon Graphics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6693462133407593,
            "question": "Which website belongs to Silicon Graphics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6366710066795349,
            "question": "How do you access the website for Silicon Graphics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6124780178070068,
            "question": "What is the online address for Silicon Graphics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6056336164474487,
            "question": "What is the web address for Silicon Graphics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5650599598884583,
            "question": "Give me the web address of Silicon Graphics."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5602763891220093,
            "question": "Where can you find information about Silicon Graphics online?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5431056022644043,
            "question": "What is the internet address for Silicon Graphics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47093114256858826,
            "question": "Where would you go online to learn more about Silicon Graphics?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The URL of Silicon Graphics is //www.sgi.com.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5017_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the internet address for Silicon Graphics?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5017_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can you find information about Silicon Graphics online?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5017_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Give me the web address of Silicon Graphics.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5017_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5017_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5017_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5017_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5017_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5017_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5017_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5017_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5017_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5017_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5017_65.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n**Triple:** Silicon Graphics (SGI) was a developer and manufacturer of Graphics Workstation.\n\n**Context information:** \n\n* file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5017/re-ranker-msmarco/15.txt\n* Text: Silicon Graphics (SGI) was a developer and manufacturer of Graphics Workstation, their computers were considered by many to be gold standard for high-end 3D graphics from the early 80s to the mid-2000s...\n\n**Evaluation:** The information in the document supports the triple. Therefore:\n\n`{ \"output\": \"yes\" }`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: None of the provided documents contain information about the URL of Silicon Graphics, Inc. Therefore, the statement \"The URL of Silicon Graphics is //www.sgi.com\" cannot be confirmed or supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'no'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information provided contains a variety of sources, including Wikipedia, which states that Silicon Graphics was known as SGI (Silicon Graphics International), and the company's own website, which does not use the URL //www.sgi.com.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}